Guide to the G. William Skinner papers, 1948-1988, 1951-1958 (bulk).
Skinner, G. William papers
- Series V. 1957-1962, 1957 Survey and Early Analysis
  - SMAK I (PSKD) Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 17-19)
    - SMAK I (PSKD) 7001-7020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - SMAK I (PSKD) 7021-7040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - SMAK I (PSKD) 7041-7049, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - SMAK (PSKDII) Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 20-22)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMAK (PSKDII) High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - SMAK (PSKDII) 7101-7120, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - SMAK (PSKDII) 7121-7140, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - SMAK (PSKDII) 7141-7154, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - SMA Nusantara X001-X022, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMA Nusantara High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
  - Rejected Questionnaires, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
    These are mostly incomplete questionnaires that were not included in the data analysis.
    - Rejected Questionnaires I, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Rejected Questionnaires II, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Canisius Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 26-29)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Canisius High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - Canisius 8001-8020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Canisius 8021-8040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Canisius 8041-8060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Canisius 8061-8073, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Sancta Ursula Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
    1957 Survey administered to students of Sancta Ursula High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - Sancta Ursula 8101-8120, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Sancta Ursula 8121-8140, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Sancta Ursula 8141-8149, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - SMA IIIB Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 4-7)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMA IIIB High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - SMA IIIB 9001-9020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - SMA IIIB 9021-9040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - SMA IIIB 9041-9060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - SMA IIIB 9061-9085, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - SMA IV Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 8-14)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMA IV High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - SMA IV 9101-9120, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - SMA IV 9121-9140, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - SMA IV 9141-9160, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - SMA IV 9161-9180, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - SMA IV 9181-9200, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - SMA IV 9201-9220, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - SMA IV 9221-9237, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - SMA IIB Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMA IIB High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - SMA IIB 9301-9320, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - SMA IIB 9321-9334, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - SMA JMIK Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 17-20)
    1957 Survey administered to students of SMA JMIK High School in Jakarta; in Indonesian.
    - SMA JMIK 0001-0020, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - SMA JMIK 0021-0040, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - SMA JMIK 0041-0060, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - SMA JMIK 0061-0070, Original questionnaires, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Series VI. 1963-1988, Sibling Status and Statistical Analysis
  - 1968 Data Run Codes (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Sibling Status Papers (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Filial Sons and Their Sisters: Configuration and Culture in Chinese Families (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Family Structure and Politics in Modern China (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - The Study of Sibling Position: A Programmatic Statement (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Preliminary Seminar Report: Personality and Motivation in Chinese Society (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Cross-sex Siblings and Political Socialization in Chinese Society (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Comments on Delia Davin’s paper "Women in the Countryside of China" (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Reference Materials I (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Reference Materials II (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Sibling Position and Kinship (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Large Sibsets - Full Data on Configuration (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Taiwan Sibling Position (Students’ Papers) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence and References (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Sibling Status Analysis (CC) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sibling Status Analysis (IC) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Model and Expected Frequencies (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Codebook - Deck 7 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Girls Frequency Analysis (Complete) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Lecture (Sibling Position) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Sibling Status Work Papers (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Sample Frequency Analysis (Sib-set Size) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Girls Frequency Analysis (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Other Papers on Weighting (Girls) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Sample Frequency Analysis (Sex Discrimination) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Asli, Totok, and Peranakan Analysis (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Basic Tables (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Dataset Analysis (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sex and Political Alignment (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sibling Study Printouts I (1984) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sibling Study Printouts II (1984) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Asil, Totok, and Peranakan Analysis (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Basic Tables (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dataset Analysis (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 1988 Analysis (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Oversize items, printed and hand drawn maps, Various (Box 13)
- Series VII. 1963-1988, Printouts
  - Hokkien-Javanese Acculturation Study Printouts, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Hokkien-Javanese Acculturation Study Printouts and analysis, 1963 (Box 19-20)
  - Sibling Status Analysis, 1966-1968 (Box 19-20)
  - Factor Analysis Printouts, (1966-) (Box 15)
  - Analysis Comparing Male Totok Chinese and Male Javanese, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Sibling Status Study Statistical Printouts/Analysis Printouts, Oct 1987 - Apr 1988 (Box 17)
  - Sibling Status Study Statistical Printouts/Analysis Printouts, Oct 1987 - Apr 1988 (Box 18)